myorganogold.com 2018-10-16

# Privacy Policy – Organo Gold

_Last modified: 31 May 2018_

This Privacy Policy explains how Organo Gold (“OG,” “we,” “us,” or “our”) collects, uses, and discloses your information. We have created this Privacy Policy to demonstrate our firm commitment to protecting your personal information. This Privacy Policy applies to transactions and activities in which you engage with us. Each time you visit the OG website or provide us with information, you consent to the use of your information as described in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy may be modified periodically.

### Overview

As part of the normal operation of our services we collect information about you. This Privacy Policy describes what information we collect about you and what may happen to that information. By accepting this Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions, you expressly consent to our use and disclosure of your personal information in the manner prescribed in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the OG website user agreement. Personal information is information that can be used to directly or indirectly identify you and it also includes anonymous information that is linked to information that can be used to directly or indirectly identify you. Personal information does not include information that has been irreversibly anonymized or aggregated so that it can no longer enable us, whether in combination with other information or otherwise, to identify you.

### How We May Collect or Receive Information from You

OG may collect or receive your personal data from you through your use of the Website in various ways. You may choose to submit your personal data and other information to us through various communication channels provided on the “Contact Us” webpage of the Website, for example, e-mail addresses, telephone numbers or online forms. You may browse the OG website without revealing any personal information about yourself, however once you wish to actually use the features available on the OG website, you will not be able to retain your anonymity. In order to fully meet your needs and provide you with an efficient and enjoyable experience, as well as providing access to certain features that may be of interest to you, we may require personal information. This may include things such as your full name, postal address, phone number, email address, billing information, shipping information, financial information (debit or credit card numbers and other card information) or demographic information (information that you submit, or that we collect, that is neither personal information nor financial information; this may include, but is not limited to, zip code, postal code, hometown, gender, username, age, birth date, purchase history information, browsing history information, searching history information, registration history information, and the content of communications between you and other users over the OG website. Demographic information is either “non-public information”, which consists of user history information and one-on-one communications between you and other users of the OG website, or “public information”, which consists of all other demographic information. We ask that you do not enter personal information or financial information into a publicly viewed area (for example, don’t use your address or password as your username, or include your name or address in written communications or item descriptions), because if you do then it will then become “public information.” You always have the option to not provide specific information by choosing not to use a particular service or feature.

Like most e-commerce Websites, each time you visit the OG website, we automatically collect your IP address and the web page from which you came. In order to administer and optimize the OG website for you and to diagnose problems with the OG website, we use your IP address only to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information about you.

If you choose to post messages in our Forum, chat rooms, message areas (this may include, but is not limited to Twitter, Facebook and similar) or leave feedback for other users, we will collect that information you have provided. This information will be reviewed by us as necessary to provide customer support, diagnose technical problems, and resolve disputes.

A specific file may be retained for you regarding any direct correspondence to us, such as emails or letters, or if other users or third parties send us correspondence about your activities or postings on the Site.

Your buying, selling, and browsing habits on the OG website are automatically tracked for the purpose of our own research on our users’ demographics, interests, and behavior in order to better understand, protect and serve you and our online community. This may include the site that you just came from, the one that you will visit next, your computer browser information, and your IP address.

As a global company, OG has a number of corporate affiliates in different jurisdictions. Each of these affiliates collects, processes and determines how to process your personal information to help providing you with the services you request.

We may use cookies or similar technologies that collect certain Website usage information when you access, view and use the Website. A cookie is a data file placed on a computer or mobile device when it is used to visit websites

### Cookies and Similar Technologies

We use cookies and similar technologies to provide, protect, and improve our products and services, such as by personalizing content, offering and measuring advertisements, understanding user behavior, and providing a safer experience.  
You can remove or reject cookies using your browser or device settings, but in some cases doing so may affect your ability to use our products and services.

Please read our Cookie Statement to learn more about how we use cookies and the choices you have.

### Cookie Statement

**WHAT ARE COOKIES?**  
Cookies are small files that are stored on your computer’s hard drive when you visit a website.

**WHAT DO COOKIES DO?**  
Cookies do lots of different jobs, such as letting you navigate between pages efficiently and enhancing the customer’s experience when visiting a website. For example they can remember your preferences.  
Yes, cookies are small text files. They can’t look into your computer or read any personal information. Cookies can’t carry viruses or install anything harmful on your computer.

**ARE COOKIES USED FOR TRACKING?**  
Yes, we also use cookies to track how many people are visiting our website and also which areas of the site they are viewing. This gives us an insight into how our customers are using our website and helps us to improve usability.

**WHAT TYPES OF COOKIES ARE USED?**  
We use a number of cookies; these are session cookies and persistent cookies. These cookies do not collect personal information.

Session Cookies: These cookies identify that the user is moving from page to page and terminate when the user stops visiting the various pages. It is then deleted when the browser is closed.

Persistent Cookies: These cookies help us to remember your settings when you revisit our website and therefore these continue to stay on your computer after you have visited our site.

Third Party Cookies: All cookies belong to an owner such as advertising partners and can also be set into external content from third party websites within our website.

**SHOULD I KEEP COOKIES SWITCHED ON?  
** We would like you to keep cookies ‘turned on’ while you visit our websites so you receive the best possible experience. However if you would like to turn off cookies you can do so by editing the settings in your browser.

Turn off cookies in Internet Explorer >> Click here [(http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows7/Block-enable-or-allow-cookies)](http://windows.microsoft.com/en-US/windows7/Block-enable-or-allow-cookies)  
Turn off cookies in Chrome >> Click here [ (https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en)](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/95647?hl=en)  
Turn off cookies in Safari >> Click here [(https://support.apple.com/kb/ph11913?locale=en_US)](https://support.apple.com/kb/ph11913?locale=en_US)  
Turn off cookies in FireFox >> Click here [(https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Enabling+and+disabling+cookies)](https://support.mozilla.org/en-US/kb/enable-and-disable-cookies-website-preferences?redirectlocale=en-US&redirectslug=Enabling+and+disabling+cookies)  
Turn off cookies in Safari IOS >> Click here [(https://support.apple.com/en-gb/HT201265)](https://support.apple.com/en-gb/HT201265)  
Turn off cookies in Google Android >> Click here [ (https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/2392971?hl=en&ref_topic=3422740)](https://support.google.com/chrome/answer/2392971?hl=en&ref_topic=3422740)

By using this website you are confirming you are happy to accept the use of cookies.

### Information Others Collect From You

This Privacy Policy only applies to the use and disclosure of information that OG collects from you. On our website, we place links to other websites operated by other parties. Some of these other websites contain our brand names and trademarks and other intellectual property that we own; others do not. When you click on these links and visit these other websites, regardless of whether or not they contain our brand names, trademarks and other intellectual property, you need to be aware that we do not control these other websites or these other websites’ business practices, and that this Privacy Policy does not apply to these other websites

Consequently, the operators of these other websites may collect different kinds of information about you, and may use and disclose that information in different ways than we would if it were collected on the OG website. This concept also applies to your disclosure of information to any other parties. We encourage you to review their privacy policies and remind you that we will not be responsible for their actions.

### How We Use Your Personal Information

We use your personal information to help us efficiently operate the OG website, to contact you in connection with your transactions and other activities on the OG website, to forward messages to you from other users, to correct problems, collect service fees, gather demographic information, analyze data to improve your experience, enforce our distributor agreement, resolve user disputes, protect against fraud or criminal activity, and inform you of offers, updates or services that might be of interest. These types of communications are known as “Operational Communications.” In some cases, Operational Communications may also contain commercial messages, such as banner ads and special offers. It is our policy not to sell or rent to any to third parties, your personal information for any purpose without your expressed consent. We may however, gather personal demographic data which may be disclosed in a manner that is not personally identifiable, for the purpose third party marketing analysis. This would not include your name, financial account numbers, email, or passwords.

We also use personal information to send you newsletters, information, offers and other promotional materials for OG’s or third parties’ goods or services. We attempt to send you offers that are of value to you, such as discounts, or exclusive offers. The OG website provides you with options to decline to receive communications from the OG website (other than those contained in Operational Communications). Some of these options may only be for a certain category of communications; others may be more general. If you wish to stop receiving certain communications, you have the option to do so by changing your user preferences.

In order to operate the OG website, including processing your transactions and supporting your activities, it may be necessary for us to share your personal information with our internal agents, representatives, contractors and service providers so they can provide us with support services such as authorization of credit card transactions, billing, affiliate programmes, email origination, receipt or support services, customer relationship management services, order fulfilment and promotional fulfilment. We require these entities by confidentiality agreement, not to use your information for any other purpose without your expressed permission.

By purchasing, or registering or making reservations for, products or services offered or sponsored by third parties on the OG website, or electing to receive communications, or electing to participate in contests, prize draws or other programmes, offered or sponsored by third parties on the OG website, you are providing some degree of your personal information specifically to those third parties. Those third parties may use your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. You will need to contact those third parties to instruct them directly regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information by them. You should evaluate any third party’s privacy practices before using their services. Additionally, you agree that we may use and disclose all such information so submitted to such third parties in the same manner in which we are entitled to use and disclose any other information you submit to us.

In some cases, we may enter into a promotional relationship with another company in which we prominently display their brand name or trademarks on pages of the OG website. These pages are known as “Co-Branded Pages” and these companies are known as “Co-Branded Companies.” If the page on which you submit information is a Co-Branded Page, or was accessed by clicking on a link on a Co-Branded Page, then we may share some of your e-mail information with the associated Co-Branded Company. Co-Branded Companies may use your personal information in accordance with their own privacy policies. You will need to contact Co-Branded Companies to instruct them directly regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information by them.

Any third party with whom you expressly allow us to share your personal information is authorized to use your personal information in accordance with our contractual arrangements with such third parties and in accordance with their own privacy policies, over which we have no control, and you agree that we are not responsible or liable for any of their actions or omissions. Those who contact you will need to be instructed directly by you regarding your preferences for the use of your personal information by them.

We cannot ensure that any of your and other personal information or private communications will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. We may be forced to disclose personal information to the government or third parties under certain circumstances, transmissions or private communications may be unlawfully intercepted or accessed by third parties, or other users may abuse or misuse your personal information that they collect from the OG website. Therefore, although we use industry high standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personal information or private communications will always remain private.

### How We Use Your Financial Information

We use your financial information only to check your qualifications, verify your identity and credibility, to bill you for products and services, and to enable you to participate in discount, rebate and similar programs in which you may elect to participate. By making a purchase, or engaging in any other kind of activity or transaction that uses financial information, on the OG website, you consent to us providing your financial information to our internal service providers as we determine is necessary to support and process your activities and transactions, as well as to your debit or credit card issuer for their purposes. These third parties may include the debit or credit card companies and banking institutions used to process and support the transaction or activity. By purchasing, or registering or making reservations for, products or services of other third parties offered on the OG website, or by participating in programs offered on the OG website that are administered by third parties and that require you to submit financial information in order to use them, you also consent to our providing your financial information to those third parties.

### Special Cases in which we share Personal and Financial Information

We may disclose personal information or financial information when we determine that such disclosure is necessary to comply with applicable law, to cooperate with law enforcement or to protect the interests or safety of OG, its distributors, or other visitors to the OG website. Whenever personal information or financial information is disclosed under this paragraph, we may also disclose your demographic information along with it, on a non-anonymous basis.

OG will cooperate with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties in the interest of enforcing laws, preventing criminal activity, protecting rights (including intellectual property), and protecting you and our OG community from harmful or criminal acts. Therefore, if we receive a verified request by government officials or other law enforcement agencies regarding an alleged illegal activity or investigation, you authorize us to disclose any of your personal information or history without a subpoena. In an effort to respect your privacy however, we will not otherwise disclose your personal information to law enforcement or other government officials without a subpoena, court order or substantially similar legal procedure, unless we believe that such information is necessary to prevent imminent physical harm or financial loss, or to report suspected illegal activity. You also authorize us to disclose your personal and account information under confidentiality agreement, as we in our sole discretion believe necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy, or other unlawful activity.

### Our Security Precautions

All of OG’s website user information is stored on secure servers within the United States, and protected by applicable Federal laws. OG has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control, and that which is exchanged on OG website. Our secure server software (SSL) is the industry high standard and among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. We encrypt all of your personal and financial information as it travels over the Internet and we store your financial information on our servers in encrypted form.

### How you may use the Information of other Users. (For independent distributors only)

OG grants its independent distributors limited access to other distributors’ email, ID, and shipping information, in order to allow interaction among everyone within the OG community. Through the acceptance of Terms of Use, you agree that you have authority to use other users’ personal information that you obtain through the OG site, through related communication, or any OG-facilitated transaction, only for using services offered through OG and communications that are not unsolicited commercial messages, or for any other purpose that a user expressly agrees to. Users must have an opportunity to have you remove any information you have collected about them. In addition, under no circumstances, you can disclose personal information about another user to any third party without our consent and the consent of that user. You agree that other users may use your personal information to communicate with you regarding OG related matters. Note that law enforcement personnel, and other rights holders are given different rights with respect to information they access.

OG and its service providers do not tolerate “spam”. Therefore, you DO NOT have any authority or permission whatsoever to add any reference to “OG”, “Organo Gold” or to otherwise insinuate that any electronic message you communicate to third parties has any affiliation whatsoever with the Company. Regardless of whom it is you are communicating with — be it a purchaser, fellow Distributor, or even the Company itself — AND, regardless where the message originates from — be it from another Distributor, your business organization, or even the Company itself — ABSOLUTELY NO MESSAGES SENT BY to you or your e-mail address should include any reference, or insinuation of approbation of the communication by the Company.

The Company has a ZERO TOLERANCE policy regarding any act which violates the above Policy. Be forewarned, if the above provision is not observed, then OG will take appropriate legal action.

### Children

We do not knowingly collect, use, or disclose information from children under 16. Anyone under 16 years of age is considered a child and is not eligible to utilize our services, and we ask that those under the age of 16, do not submit any personal, private, or financial information to us. If you are a child, you may use OG’s site only in conjunction with a parent or legal guardian consent.

If we learn that we have collected the personal information of a child under 16, we will take steps to delete the information as soon as possible. Please immediately email [support@organogold.com](mailto:support@organogold.com "Email Organo Gold Support") if you become aware that a child under 16 has provided us with personal information.

### Your Rights

We take reasonable steps to ensure that your personal information is accurate, complete, and up-to-date.

You have the right under applicable law to access, correct, or delete the personal information that we collect. You are also entitled to object to or restrict, at any time, the further processing of your personal information. You have the right to receive your personal information in a structured and standard format. You may lodge a complaint with the competent data protection authority regarding the processing of your personal information.

To protect the privacy and the security of your personal information, we may request information from you to enable us to confirm your identity and right to access such information, as well as to search for and provide you with the personal information we maintain. There are instances where applicable laws or regulatory requirements allow or require us to refuse to provide or delete some or all of the personal information that we maintain.

You may email [support@organogold.com](mailto:support@organogold.com "Email Organo Gold Support") to exercise your rights. We will respond to your request in a reasonable timeframe, where possible within 30 days. If your request is more complicated, it may take a little longer to come back to you but we will come back to you within two months of your request. There is no charge for most requests, but if you ask us to provide a significant about of data for example we may ask you to pay a reasonable admin fee. We may also ask you to verify your identity before we provide any information to you.  
You may alter or update the personal, financial, or demographic information that you have given us by manually making the modifications in the sections of the OG website in which you originally submitted that information.

These changes and deletions will not change or delete emails or information that we may have already forwarded to other users or credit card companies or any other third parties, all as provided above in this Privacy Policy.

Upon your request, we will deactivate your account, contact information, billing information, shipping information, and financial information from our active databases. To make this request, please email [support@organogold.com .](mailto:support@organogold.com "Email Organo Gold Support") It may be necessary for some of the personal information that you have requested to remove, to be retained by OG for the purpose of collecting any fees owed, diagnosing problems, assisting with any legal investigations, resolving disputes, preventing criminal activity, or enforcing our User Agreement. Therefore, you should not expect that all of your information will be completely removed from our files or databases in response to your requests. However, such personal information will only be available to selected OG personal, and will no longer be accessible to other users or the public.

### How Long We Keep Your Information

We keep your data only for as long as we need it. How long we need data depends on what we are using it for, whether that is to provide services to you, for our own legitimate interests (described above) or so that we can comply with the law.

We will actively review the information we hold and when there is no longer a distributor, customer, legal or business need for us to hold it, we will either delete it securely or in some cases anonymise it.

### How to Manage Marketing Messages You Receive

We may send you marketing communications by email if you have indicated that you are happy to receive such emails or if you have transacted with us and you have not told us that you no longer wish to receive marketing emails. You can update your preferences at any time. You can also opt out of receiving marketing emails by clicking on the unsubscribe link which we include in all our marketing emails.

Our marketing communications include information about our new and existing products and/or services, special offers we think you might like and other products or programmes which we think might be useful to you.

Please note that if you tell us that you do not wish to receive marketing emails, you will still receive service emails which are necessary for example to confirm your purchases or to update you on the status of your orders. This is so that we can perform the contract we have with you.

Please note that if you ask us to stop sending marketing emails, we will keep a note of your personal information and your request so that we can make sure you are excluded from the emails when they are sent out.

### Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may change this Privacy Policy to be in line with industry practices or regulatory requirements. Your continued use of our website and services after the effective date of the Privacy Policy means that you accept the revised Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to the revised Privacy Policy, please refrain from using our website or services and contact us to close any account you may have created.

### Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the Site, or your dealings with the OG website. Please contact us at [support@organogold.com](mailto:support@organogold.com "Email Organo Gold Support")

**ORGANO™ GOLD Enterprises Inc**  
12148 Horseshoe Way  
Richmond, BC V7A 4V5
